See the three.
We having now the two new teams
joining in the contest.
Aon versus Lockton. Aon won the decided
to bat first.
Okay, we are all in readiness.
Rahul Panchchal on strike. Mitesh on
non-strike. Jraj sings into count of
five 4 3 2 1. Here we go.
First two overs two field outside circle
30 at circle one at longoff and one at
cow corner.
Kerfield a bit
at mid wicket now.
First ball. Here we go.
And first ball. Good strike by captain
Rahul Panchal.
Mites Johan
now on strike.
final.
Good strike from Mites.
Two ball five for no loss
and they will capitalize more runs in
the power play.
That's very good fielding. Good bowling.
Good bowling. In fact,
an excellent tap and play and single.
Good come back from Jiraj.
Multiple shot by Gaprias.
switch hit looking to play
but uh then he thought it was not coming
on the bat just left and went for that
ball.
A quick single taken
J Singh.
Long
one was gone.
A on eight for no loss.
After Jay Singh uh Ramak Krishnan
the tall man comes into the attack.
So one more over in the power play.
One at one at Longoff and one fielder at
cow corner
mites strike
and that's high in the air.
Oh that was a bit
great effort. We can say in fact
and it's very tough to take that reverse
catch and while running
will take two runs in that location.
There is something different strategy
the bowl that shot Bish L allowing the
batsman to hit for big one.
He's got that outside edge and very good
stop by the fielder at short. Third man
single taken
score
team Aon Roy Panchal the captain on
strike.
and up and over. Very well played. That
will go all the way for four runs.
Music.
That's very well played. Deep backward
point for four.
They're waiting for yo-yo singer.
and R was looking to play for big one. A
bit of fumble there but no runs taken.
Rama Krishnan
eight runs conceded in four balls.
Solar and Kitney.
Last two balls in the power play
and Ra Pancha looking for
some big fireworks.
Short
beat.
No runs.
16 for no loss.
And it was like a bit of lost his
balance. The fielder had covers and
because of that he was about to take
that catch
but that's being put down.
Still a good attempt to stop.
Two has gone 17 for none.
They're going for two runs and they will
get two runs.
Team A1. They were the runnerup of the
season two of the Brokers Premier League
2024.
And the winner was MIBL. And this time
he connects. This time he got a success.
Captain Royal Panchchal striking really
well. 13 of nine with two fours.
Ter team Aon.
Oh, that's stumping out and gone.
>> The first wicket fall and good bowling
from Ajay Singh
stepping out from the crease and looking
to play for big one and completely
missed it. Anurag has done the job
behind the storm. 13 of 10 with two
fours and captain departs Rahul
Panchchal
2.3 23 for one team Aon
Tina pis.
Wow. Innovation
reverse
and that will go all the way for four
runs. Kunal ta into the bowling attack.
Mitesh Johan 14 of two force 29 for one.
Very well left by the batter to get the
extra runs and quick run taken wide.
Plus one run.
31 for one.
Siddesh Moy on strike.
Siddesh Bora last year I still remember
he's played a fantastic batting
he was one of the top in the most
valuable player MVP Siddesh Moore Okay.
One of the top contenders in the list in
the previous uh year of the Brokers
Premier League 2024.
That's very good bowling once again.
with a single 33 for one. Sidesh Mur
back on strike.
That's a good strike into the block
hole. They're going for two runs. Chance
for the run out and gone.
Just short of the crease. Good throw
from long gone fielder and that's a one
more wicket fall.
It was very quick run between bit the
wicket but the fielder was too quick
then the batters accident throw.
34 for two. Last ball. I do four over
coming up.
Sidesh on strike.
Oh, that's gone. Bold back to back. The
team locked in has got the wicket of
Aon. They're just hitting at the top of
the stumps.
The timber shattered, dreams scattered
of Siddesh Mur.
So one wicket fall
four was gone. 34 for three.
And this time that's played a hook shot.
Four runs at backward region.
Short pitch ball and excellent timing.
38 for three. Last four balls coming up
of the first innings.
The score is 39 for three. Last three
balls coming up. Will they get 45 plus
Prrenit Pab
on strike?
That's a good strike.
and all the way for four runs at long
region.
We're talking about that 45. They got 43
now with that boundary and two ball left
of the innings coming up.
So when mid expensive Ramak Krishnan 1.4
18 runs
we'll come back. Let's see.
Oh yes, that's a good comeback. We just
talked about
43 for three.
Last ball coming up. Will he get a
wicket or Pranit Para will look for big
one?
Off linear
Mr. Home Singh signaling wide
44 for three a hit 50 score.
Not easy to hit big shots uh on this
ground especially.
Good strike
for a single
and yes that's out. So two runs 46 for
four after five and 47 to win for team
Lton.
So very well played by team Aon.
47 to win for team lockton.
We'll take a short break and come back.
Meanwhile, music
Hello and welcome back once again to the
ICIC Lombard presents
and proudly presenting this third season
at the iconic cricket ground Fatima
grounds Vidya Mumbai.
Brokers Premier League 2026 season 3
47 the target to chase for the team
Lockton and Rahul Panchal
setting up the field the skipper of Aon
All in readiness we are Anurag Ryan
strike Nathan Wa on n on strike and
Ankur Jane will start the resetings.
So umpires are ready, fielders are
ready, batters are ready and all
expected are ready.
So game on 3 2 1 and game on.
Here we go. First ball 47 to chase
in 30 balls.
Very
well left. Starting with the extras down
the leg side for wide.
Looking for big one. No run. Sent back.
So keeping the eye on the fielder at
short mid wicket Anuragan Ry denied to
take that single Nitan VHMA he says that
no need to take risk right now good
observation
this time they'll take a single run
two for no loss and Nitin WMA will face
the first
chance for the catch and being put down.
Pressure lock team
luck in the favor of team lockton
looking to play for big one has got that
outside edge there's a fieldielder
standing at short third man for single
And that will run away for four runs at
fine leg region. Easy be easy picking up
short short pitch ball and that's a good
strike from Nitan Wma
and that's what every over nine runs 10
runs
they can get this target win of 47 to
chase for the team lockton
last ball of the first over eight for no
loss
And that's up and over of the fielder
and that will run away for four rounds.
Wow, good batting.
So one was gone, 12 for no loss.
Excellent start from team Lockton.
Char over run
the required run is 8.75 and they
started with 12 runs and that's what
Nitan Wman Anuragaray
Anurakra will play the anchor role and
Nitan WHMA has already got two
boundaries good start one 12 for no loss
and 35 runs in 24 balls
Deep back deep backward point
and one fielder at deep mid wicket.
That's two fielder outside the circle.
Long gone is brought back to mid on.
Something uh will come in this over for
sure. Sidesh Mur
high in the air.
They will stop
and good stop by the fielder at midn
long on region
and two runs taken. Good batting from
Anurag Ry.
Now there's a change in field settings.
Midon is going long and deep backward
point fielder is coming at point inside
the circle. So one fielder at mid wicket
and one fielder at long
and again there is a field setting
change. Long on is brought back. Mid on.
And there's a fielder at long off now.
Long off and mid wicket.
That will land safe for sure. And
captain Rahul Panchal was running to
take that catch.
We'll get a single 15 for no loss.
It's Barbing.
fielding.
Long off or long on fielder?
Outside the circle
or direct hit
per
just in time. 16 for no loss. One run
taken.
That's a quick running from Nithan.
31 runs from 20 balls
down the track. Very well played.
But there's a fielder at Longorn.
And direct hit. And this time gone.
Wow.
Take a ball for that player. A very
good. It was unfortunately hit on the
Stums. He never thought it was hitting
on the Stums. It was very good throw.
And that's a wicket fall.
First wicket of team Lockton.
So good throw from Shashank there. He's
got the big man out. Nitan Wa
>> really batteratted well. 105 with two
fours. 1.57 for one.
30 runs in coming 3.1.
That's 19 balls and 30 runs to get.
is
again
Singh
Dham Shandara.
Lockton. Yeah. Aon
music.
so two go 21 for
one.
So Shashan got promoted after hitting
the direct hit from the long
He was looking to play fine towards fine
leg
and that will go all the way for four
runs. Yes,
the ball went towards that square leg
region.
There's something confusion
in the fielding side but that will run
away for four.
Wow. What was that? What was that? What
a good turn.
That was a good turn from Shashank.
22 runs, 14 balls.
It's going wide outside the off line. 21
from 14.
He's got that outside edge.
Looking London talking Tokyo
and single run. They will get 20 runs
and 13 balls. Need that one big hit to
get the equation closer.
Last ball of the third over coming up 20
from 13.
That's again a wide ballot
bowling. Seven runs conceded by
Shashank.
Three go. 28 for one. Locked in 19 runs
and 12 balls.
Now captain Rah Panchchal comes into the
attack.
Very crucial over of the match.
17 from 11. Now
Anur Ry on strike
has got that 14 and Jiraj also got 14.
So two big destructive batters on the
crease.
and catches wins matches. Rahul Panchcha
the captain strikes
looking to play on side. The ball went
offside at covers region. A simple catch
and that's a very important breakthrough
that team Aon needed and they got it.
10 balls and 17 runs now for the team
lock
and good cash taken by Abinandra at
covers.
They're looking for two runs and they'll
get it. Rama Krishnan.
He just need four five steps. He is a
tall man to run the 23 yards.
No,
very good bowling from Rahul Panchal.
And that will go all the way for six run
into the com box.
Excellent timing. So beautiful. So
elegant. So damar, so damakar
just looking like a wow.
That was the biggest of the night.
And it was catching chance for NRO GI
also. It was well besides beside of me
also it was catching chance for me also.
They're looking for two only a single
run that one big six made the impact
completely.
Seven runs
in six balls.
So team Aon and team lockton Gega by
Gega
Gega by Gega.
If you're supporting team Aon, make some
noise.
If you are SUPPORTING TEAM LOCK, MAKE
some noise.
Team lock show meter
seven run six ball crazy atmosphere
and let's see very interesting match in
progress at Fatima grounds
seven run six balls
The strong candidate Siddesh Mori
into the attack.
Here we go.
Just a single channel run out there
but quickly into the crease.
Excellent bowling from Siddesh and oh
that could be the runout chance.
Single run charan.
All eyes on this match.
All eyes on Siddish Mur. All eyes on
Jayat Singh.
Charan
and that's gone high in the air.
They go for two runs.
Two runs. Three ball and three runs.
Runner ball. Easy. Three singles and
that's it. But now we need to check
whether team Aon will set up that
attacking fielding or will be the same
what they are currently right now the
field setup
three ball three runs.
just played with soft hands with single
and two ball too needed. Now
they're not taking risk. They're not
going for big one.
Dog gain or do run.
So bit of silence in the crowd. Gega
Ga.
Let's see Lton or Aon.
cricket.
Two ball and two runs. Interesting to
watch. A very crucial ball coming up of
the match.
OH, CLEAN BALL. WOW. OH, GOOD BOWLING
FROM SIDESH MOR.
TIMBER SHATTERED, DREAM SCATTERED.
One two needed
and team Aon on the money. Siddesh on
the money.
Siddesh
experienced contender
bowling.
Here we go once again. We'll ask
lock.
One ball, two runs.
What a mad this is.
Two runs and one ball. Still
duck duck. Duck duck duck duck dug duck
dug duck.
Here
we go. Two runs, one ball
and they will go for two for sure and
this will be like oh
that's SCORES A LEVEL AND we are
expecting
Come team.
The first super over coming up of the
ICA Lombard presents Brokers Premier
League 2026
Season 3.
Music. Music.
Okay, here we go.
Super our first ball.
Sideshi will start. Jay on strike. Nitin
WHMA on strike.
Let's play.
And that's wicked first ball. And
remember only two wickets. Then that's
it. That's the end of the that first
innings. So they got one wicket very
early. And now last wicket coming up.
So good fielding side from team Aon.
And now it will be the last wicket. If
they got one more wicket then that's it.
That's end of the first inning of super
over.
Anurag, the new batter, walks in.
Oh, just
no runs. In fact, that was you just in
the air. Very good stop.
We'll get a single run.
The first run into the account of the
super over
And yes, that's it. That's the end of
the first of Super Over. Good cash
taken. So they need only
four runs.
Okay. So, only one run. So, only two
runs needed. There's a bit of correction
from my side.
So, only two runs needed. Matra Doran.
One for two. Good bowling attack from
team Aon.
So only two runs, one for two
and this will be like a ball match. It's
So only two runs needed and captain ro
panchal mitan strike or
doran
coming this first ball very first ball
will go for the two runs or boundary
let's
two to win. First ball.
Oh, single tick and so level and only
one needed.
Here
we go. Just one needed
for the team Aon. And that's it.
Team Aon got the victory.